[{"answer": "Well, two things, Piers.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "What is wrong with that in principle?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well, even the president himself.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Those who got more, help out a little bit more?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, as to Mitt Romney, he has released his tax returns and for multiple years.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Because if it was the other way around and it was Barack Obama who had all these secret accounts in Switzerland, the Cayman Islands and so on, you guys would be banging for blood to get this information out there, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Well, to be fair, when Governor Romney first addressed it himself, he said, obviously, it's a tax.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "That kind of flip-flopping doesn't help, does it?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Well, this election isn't going to be decided by the vice presidency, whether it's Joe Biden or whoever Mitt Romney ends up selecting.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Are you going to give me the normal pat, \"I have absolutely no interest in that\" answer, or is there something else you can tell me?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Well, we don't talk about the process, Piers, in terms of timing or the nature of the process.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Are you being vetted at the moment?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Well, I find it so interesting.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "What do you make of what Tim Pawlenty just said?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Well, if you read the Americans for Tax Reform pledge there are carve-outs for things like national security in times of war.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Isn't that what a sort of modern smart democracy does?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "My household does and my business certainly does.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Without being too personal about your finances, Kelly, I mean do you -- do you earn more than $250,000 a year?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "$250,000 is a lot of money, isn't it?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "To your point about how many people make $250,000 a year, it's less -- 98 percent of people in the United States make less than that.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "What do you have to say?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "Yes, well, scientology was started by L. Ron Hubbard.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Put it into context for anyone who hears the word and has no real idea what it means?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, ever since I left the Moonies in 1976, I've been actually talking with people involved in scientologist, coming out of scientology.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "But if you assume that that was becoming a problem in the relationship, how easy is it to leave a scientology relationship like this?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Well, I must say something -- scientology may be working now as a religion.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "What was the experience like for you?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "It depends on your experience.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Let me -- do people wildly exaggerate the scientologists?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "I think I'm entitled.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "You want answers?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Good.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Good.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "How are you doing, Piers?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Well, just as a professional actor, you couldn't have anybody who was more dedicated, more passionate about his work.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "What's he really like?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "Well, you know, a number of years ago, my mother and father celebrated their 60th wedding anniversary.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "What's been the secret to your successful marriage would you say?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's interesting to point out that here we are in the midst of the worst economy since the Great Depression and, you know, the conventional wisdom is no president has ever won re- election when the unemployment rate is above 7.5 percent, and here we are at 8.1, 8.2 percent.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "What is your overview of where the election battle currently stands?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "EINER: First of all, you used the word ridiculously, which is exactly right.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "If he gets re-elected, where would you like to see him really put his foot on the pedal?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "That's a pretty good reason.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Tell me very quickly, Rob, why should we go and watch this film, other than the fact it has the brilliant Morgan Freeman in it?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know quite what to make of it, except for the fact I think if you're going to measure on the scale of the fact that he had a white mother or that there's a mixed race of it, then I don't think we'll probably ever have any black presidents.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "What do you make of that statement, as a man who's campaigned for Obama?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "She had the most keen ability to observe this awkward dance that men and women do with each other.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "What made her so special?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "Your client is out.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "How you doing, Piers?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "It's a sort of -- it's a very weird thing to be doing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "My true opinion is that I've reviewed thousands of the supporters' comment that have come to us.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "How do you know that's not happening?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "I still think we have about six months of discovery to go.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "What is the time scale now, Mark, in terms of how you see the legal process moving forward in the next few months?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Unfortunately, he's not entitled to any state provided security.", "docId": "120709pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "If he isn't, what is he doing about protecting himself in terms of security or whatever else he may be having?", "qSentId": 608}]